Guide to the Office of Administration and Facilities, Eileen Buckley 1959-1995 (Bulk 1964-1989) RG 8.0 RG 8.0
New York University Archives
- Series I: General Files
  - Presidential Fellowship/Thank You for Review Letters, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 50)
  - Presidential Lectures, undated (Box 31, Folder 51)
  - Press Annex Project/ Renovation, undated (Box 31, Folder 52)
  - Pressure Points, undated (Box 31, Folder 53)
  - Princeton University, undated (Box 31, Folder 54)
  - Project MANTREE (Stern/Uretsky), undated (Box 31, Folder 55)
  - Projects and Proposals: Private Schools, undated (Box 31, Folder 56)
  - Properties Not Owned By NYU, undated (Box 31, Folder 57)
  - Property in the Inventory, undated (Box 31, Folder 58)
  - Public Hearing Transcript: Map Change, Easterly Line, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 59)
  - Public Hearing Transcript: Urban Renewal Plan, Redevelopment Project, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 60)
  - Publicity, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058459 4
  - Purchasing, undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Pyrior, Julie Leinenger, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Quality Circle Management, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Quality Education for Minorities, undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Quayle, J. Danforth, VP, undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Quincentenary Program, 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Quincentennial General, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Quincentennial Grants, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Quincentennial-New York State Commission, undated (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Quincentennial Script for " Voices of the Encounter", undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Ratio Harrassment Policy, undated (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Rafferty, Father, 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Rafferty, Raymond, undated (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Raleigh, Frances S., undated (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Rampersad, Arnold, undated (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Raymount, Henry, undated (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Reale, Nancy M, undated (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Real Estate: Amendment, J-51, undated (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Real Estate: General, 1974-1981 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Real Estate: Meller Estate: Atlantic City Mortgage, undated (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Real Estate: NMU Upgrading, undated (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Real Estate: Property Offerings I, undated (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Real Estate: Property Offerings II, undated (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Real Estate: Property Offerings III, 1972-1983 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Real Estate: Proposed Property, 1982-1984 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Real Estate: Rector Street 2-Ebasco Building, undated (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Real Estate: Subcommitee for Real Estate Acquisition and Management, undated (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Real Estate: Subcommitee of the Board of Trustees, undated (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Real Estate: Timberlyne Property, undated (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Real Estate: Washington Square Village Buildings 1-4 (I), undated (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Real Estate: Washington Square Village Buildings 1-4, (II)hip, undated (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Rectors' Conference, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058460 2
  - Rectors' Conference, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Rectors' Conference, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Rectors' Conference General I, undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Rectors' Conference General II, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Rectors' Conference General III, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Rectors' Conference- Inaugural Escorts/Deans, undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Rectors' Conference-Letters to Ambassadors, undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Rectors' Conference-Letters to Rectors, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Rectors' Conference Proposal, undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Rectors' Conference-Rectors' Participant Forms, undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Rectors' Conference-Rejections From Rectors, undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Rectors' Conference-Thank You to Rectors, undated (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Reem, Gabriell A, Dr., undated (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Regulation-Deregulation Seminar, undated (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Registrar,Office of, undated (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Registrar,Office of, Enrollment by Racial/Ethnic Category, undated (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Reimers, Professor, undated (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Reiss, Timothy, undated (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Religious Ressurgence in the Modern Near East, undated (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Renfeild Property, Chester, New Jersey, undated (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Renwick, Fred B., undated (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Resource Planning, undated (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Reprographics, undated (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Resumes, undated (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Retirement, Uncapping of Mandatory, undated (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Rice, C. Duncan, undated (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Rice, Donald S., undated (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Rivera, Debora, undated (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Robinson, David Z., undated (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Rock, Marcia, undated (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Rockefeller University, undated (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Roesner, Edward, undated (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Rogers, Hank, undated (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Rogers, Holly, undated (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Rogers, Pier Camille, undated (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Rogers, Robin, undated (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Rose, Elihu, undated (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Rosen, Alex, undated (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Rosenzweig, Aurthur and Cynthia, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Ruperto de Ventos, Xavier, undated (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Rutenberg, James, undated (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - Sacks, Oliver, undated (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - Sagan, Eli, undated (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - Sailor's Snug Harbor, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - Sailor's Snug Harbor, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - Sailor's Snug Harbor, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 47)
  - Sailor's Snug Harbor- All Properties, undated (Box 33, Folder 48)
  - Sailor's Snug Harbor- East-West-North Block, undated (Box 33, Folder 49)
  - Sailor's Snug Harbor- Eighth Street, undated (Box 33, Folder 50)
  - Sailor's Snug Harbor- Ground Rent-Leases, undated (Box 33, Folder 51)
  - Sailor's Snug Harbor- Leases #3 and #4, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 52)
  - Sailor's Snug Harbor Properties- 5th Avenue, undated (Box 33, Folder 53)
  - Sailor's Snug Harbor Proposed Purchase, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 54)
  - Sailor's Snug Harbor- Riley, Allan J., undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058461 0
  - Sailor's Snug Harbor- Silverstein, Larry A., undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Sale Value University Owned Property, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Salvato, Michael A., undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Sarter, George, undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Saudi Arabia/Prince Bindar- Proposal to Fund Islamic Studies, undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Sawyerr, Akilagpa, undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Scarfo, Richard, undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Schechner, Richard, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Schiffman, Lawrence, undated (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Schnurman, Ned, undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Scholar Residency Program, undated (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - School Social Work, undated (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Schwartz, Delmore Poetry Award, undated (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Schwartz, Jack, undated (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Schwartz, Jacob, undated (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Schwartz, Sam, undated (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Schwartz, Victor, undated (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Sciabarra, Chris, undated (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Science Education, undated (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Scotch, David, undated (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Scott, Gloria, undated (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Scott, Jaunita S., undated (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Seaman's Church Institute, undated (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Search/Presidential Search Materials, undated (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Sedgwick Avenue-1950, undated (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Sedgwick Avenue, undated (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Sedgwick Avenue -2217, undated (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Semprum, Jorge, 1981-1991 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - SEHNAP ( School of Education), undated (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Senate- Academic Affairs, undated (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Senate- Faculty Advisement, Misconduct in Scientific Research, undated (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Senate- Minutes, undated (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Sennett, Richard, undated (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Servicemembers opportunity Colleges, undated (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Seventy-Eighth Street- 14 East, undated (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Seventh Street Residence Hall, 1965-1983 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Seville, undated (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Seville Hotel, undated (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Sexton, John, undated (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Sexual Harrassment, undated (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Sexual Harrassment Policy, undated (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - Seybold, George, undated (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - Shad, John/Proposal to Fund International Prizes, undated (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - Shakir, Adib, undated (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - Shelemay, Jack and Kay, undated (Box 34, Folder 46)
  - Shimkin Hall-Proposed Addition, undated (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - Silber, John, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058462 8
  - Silver Towers, undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Silver Towers- Garage, undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Silver Towers- General Correspondence, undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Silver Towers- Rent Increases, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Silver Towers- Concrete Sill Repairs, 1983-1985 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Silverberg, David, undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Silverstein, Larry, undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Silverstein, Larry A., undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Simoes, Antonio, undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Simon, William, undated (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Simons, Louise, undated (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Singleton, Edna, undated (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Singleton, Synovia, undated (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Sixty-Second Street-1 East/Closing Statement, undated (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Sklarew, Myra, undated (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Slappery, Mary McGowan, undated (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Sledge, Sharon, undated (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Smith, Bettie Parker, undated (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Smith, Dennis, undated (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Snyder, Peter, undated (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Social Sciences Research Council, undated (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Society of Fellows, undated (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Sofia University, undated (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Somerset County Property, undated (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Sorenson, Chris, undated (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Sorter, George, undated (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Sotirhos, Micheal G., undated (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - South African Information Exchange (SAIE), undated (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - South Africa Scholarship, undated (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Southgate Hotel, undated (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Soviet-American Center for Constitutional Democracy Proposal, undated (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Spano, Frank A, undated (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Sparrow, Roy, undated (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Sporn, Barbara, undated (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Sports Field Project, undated (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Sprague, Charles, undated (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Speeches- General, undated (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - SS Irving Berezin, undated (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - St. George Hotel, undated (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - Staray, Gloria, undated (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Statistics on University, undated (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Stedman, Harvey, undated (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - Steiner, George, undated (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - Sterling Forest, undated (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - Sterling Forest-Administration Building, undated (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - Sterling Forest-Con Ed Easement, undated (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - Sterling Forest-Conveyance to Fire Department, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 48)
  - Sterling Forest- Lemcip Project, undated (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - Sterling Forest- Maps, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 50)
  - Sterling Forest-Master Plan I, undated (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - Sterling Forest-Master Plan II, undated (Box 35, Folder 52)
  - Sterling Forest-Possible Purchase, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 53)
  - Sterling Forest- Post Sale, undated (Box 35, Folder 54)
  - Stern- Graduate School, undated (Box 35, Folder 55)
  - Stern- Joint Program with Yonsei, undated (Box 35, Folder 56)
  - Sterling Forest- Primate Colony, undated (Box 35, Folder 57)
  - Stern, Leonard/Yeshiva Study Abroad Program, undated (Box 35, Folder 58)
  - Stern, Ralph Edward, undated (Box 35, Folder 59)
  - Stony Lodge Hospital/Graduation Requirement Inquiry, undated (Box 35, Folder 60)
  - Strategic Planning Committee, undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058463 6
  - Stroke, Henry H., undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Student Involvement, undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Student Internship Programs, undated (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Stunkard, Horace, undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Sullivan, Veronica, undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Sussmith, Rita- Academic Convocation, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Stutzman, Jane, undated (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Styles, Twitty, undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Shakespeare Summer Institute, 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Summer, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Summer, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Summer, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Summer, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Summer of Service, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Summer Session, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Summer Session, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Summer Session, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Sunrise Semester, undated (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Swissweek, undated (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Takaki, Ronald T., undated (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Task Force on Residence Hall Life, undated (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Tannenbaum, William, undated (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Teaching Effectiveness, undated (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Teaching Effectiveness, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Teaching Effectiveness, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Telecommunications, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Telephone, 1987-1988 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058464 4
  - Tenth Street-58 West, undated (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Thaxton, Lorraine, undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Third Avenue-33 (I), undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Third Avenue-33 (II), undated (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Third Avenue- Architects/Voorsanger and Mills, undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Third Avenue- Bond Issue, undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Third Avenue- Budgets, undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Third Avenue- Closing Documents, undated (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Third Avenue- Community Groups, undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Third Avenue- Design Competition, undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Third Avenue- Dormitory, undated (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Third Avenue- Leasing Space Proposal, undated (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Third Avenue- Litigation, undated (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Third Avenue- News Clippings, undated (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Third Avenue- News Clippings, undated (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Third Avenue North, 1985-1986 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Third Avenue North, 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Third Avenue North- Budgets, undated (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Third Avenue North- Dormitory Authority, undated (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Third Avenue North-Morse Diesel, undated (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Third Avenue North and South- General Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Third Avenue North and South- General Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Third Avenue Plans and Designs, undated (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Third Avenue Proposed Plans, undated (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Third Avenue Proposed Plans-Graduate Dormitory, undated (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Third Avenue Retail, undated (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Third Avenue Shtino Litigation, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058465 1
  - Third Avenue Site Plans, undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Third Avenue South- 33, undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Third Avenue Tenant's Association Submission, undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Third Avenue Tobier Report- East Village Housing Trends and Market, undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Third Avenue Zoning Information, undated (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Third Street- 64-66 West (Jewish Cultural Foundation), undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Third Street- 85 West, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Third Street- 89 West (Basement Budgets), undated (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Third Street- 89-91 West, 1962-1985 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Third Street- 104 West, undated (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Third Street-104 West (Shelley Farkas), undated (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Third Street- 104 & 106 West, undated (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Thirty-Fifth Street- 310-312 East, undated (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Thirty-Fourth Street-340 East/Mayfair South Apartments (Appraisal) I, undated (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Thirty-Fourth Street-340 East/Mayfair South Apartments (Appraisal) II, undated (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Thirty-Fourth Street-332-342 East/Mayfair South Apartments (Operations), undated (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Thompson Street-131, undated (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Thompson, Marylin Berry, undated (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Title I Renovations, undated (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Tolliver, Dr. Richard Lamar, undated (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Tomasi, Lydio, undated (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Tosteson, Daniel, undated (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Town Hall (1), 1969-1973 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058466 9
  - Town Hall (2), 1975 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Town Hall- Air Rights Lease, undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Town Hall- Disposition/Sale, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Town Hall- NYU Club Lease (1), undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Town Hall- NYU Club Lease (2), undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Town Hall- Practising Law Institute Lease, undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Town Hall- Proposed Sale of Town Hall, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Trinity Place-78-86 ( AKA 111-23 Greenwich) Amex Building, undated (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - TSOA ( Tisch School of the Arts), undated (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - TSOA Budget File (1), undated (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - TSOA Budget File (2), undated (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - TSOA Construction Contracts (1), undated (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - TSOA Construction Contracts (2), undated (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - TSOA Construction Contracts (3), undated (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - TSOA Contract Extension, undated (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - TSOA Correspondence (1), undated (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - TSOA Correspondence (2), 1982 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - TSOA Correspondence (3), 1983 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - TSOA Correspondence (4), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - TSOA D & L Contract, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - TSOA Lake Contract, undated (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - TSOA Power Plant, undated (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - TSOA Savings Study, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Trachtenberg, Stephen, undated (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Treanor, Karen, undated (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Trustees, undated (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Tucker, Donna, undated (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Tutu, Bishop Desmond/Scholarships, undated (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Twelfth Street- 16-20 East (Weissman, KB), undated (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Ungerleider-Meyerson, Joy, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058467 7
  - United Nations Association, undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - United Nations High Commission for Refugees, undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - United Negro College Fund, undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - University, undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - University Buffalo, undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - University Bylaws, undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - University California-Berkeley Inauguration, undated (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - University Fall, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - University Owned Real Estate, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - University Place - 13-19 (Store Leases), undated (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - University Place - 13-19 (Zum Zum Operation), undated (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - University Place - 19, undated (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - University Place - 19, undated (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - University Plaza, undated (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - University Plaza, undated (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - University Plaza, undated (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - University Plaza, undated (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - University Plaza, undated (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - University Plaza - Picasso Sculpture, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - University - 62nd St. East - 1, undated (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - University Special Issue, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - University Special Issue, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - University Websites, undated (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - University Winter, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Upton, Arthur, undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058468 5
  - Urban Educational Proposal, undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Urban Health Care Humanities Center, undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Urquhart, Brian, undated (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - US European President's and Rector's Dinner, undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Van der Watt, Elip, undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Vance, Debby, undated (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Vanderbilt Hall - Proposed Renovations, undated (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Vice-presidents Meetings, undated (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Vice-presidents Meetings, undated (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Vice-presidents Meetings, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Vice-presidents Meetings, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Vice-presidents Meetings, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Vice-presidents Meetings, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Vice-presidents Meetings, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Vice-presidents Meetings, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Vice-presidents Meetings, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Vice-presidents Meetings Agendas, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Vice-presidents Meetings Agendas, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - VIP Day, undated (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Vidal-Beneyton, Jose, undated (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Village Alliance, undated (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Viola, Ray - Apartments & Abatements, undated (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Voorsanger, Emile, undated (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Voorsanger, Emile, undated (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Vyronis, Speros, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Wagner School Case Statements, undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058469 3
  - Wagner School of Public Service, undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Wahl, Nicholas, undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Wakeley, Cynthia, undated (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Walsh, Joseph, undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Ward, Aileen, undated (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Warren Point, undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Warren Weaver Hall, undated (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Washington Activities, undated (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Washington Place - 3-5, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Washington Place - 14, 1979-1985 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Washington Place - 14, undated (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Washington Place - 15, 1966-1982 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Washington Place - 79-81, undated (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Washington Square North - 2, undated (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Washington Square North - 19, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Washington Square North - 19, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Washington Square North - 20, 1959-1976 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Washington Square North - 21, 1983-1985 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Washington Square North - 22, undated (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Washington Square North - 22, 1963-1967 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Washington Square North - 22, 1977-1985 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Washington Square Park, undated (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Washington Square Southeast - Acquisition of Washington Square Village, undated (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Washington Square Southeast - Agreements, undated (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Washington Square Southeast - Chronological Files, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Washington Square Southeast - Chronological Files, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Washington Square Southeast - College Housing Loans, undated (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Washington Square Southeast - Correspondence, undated (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Washington Square Southeast - Cost Estimate, undated (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Washington Square Southeast - Dormitory Authority, undated (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Washington Square Southeast - Easements, undated (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Washington Square Southeast - Interuniversity Memorandom, undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058470 1